A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor John G. Pollard, 1930-1934
Library of Virginia
- Series I: General Correspondence, 1930-1934., Extent: 43.05 cu. ft. (123 boxes). (Box Boxes 1-123)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Rights of way (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Signed, 1932 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Social hygiene (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Washington County, 1932 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - General Assembly, Message material (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly, Message, 1932 (Box 50, Folder 2-3)
  - General Assembly, Reception (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly, Redistricting (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - General Assembly, 1932 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly, Opinion regarding extra session (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1933 (Box 51, Folder 1-7)
  - General Assembly (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly, Messages (Box 52, Folder 2-3)
  - General Assembly, Beer (Box 52, Folder 4-9)
  - General Assembly, Beer (Box 53, Folder 1-5)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Notes on (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Signed (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - General Assembly, Liquor Control, Appointment to Commission (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly, Liquor Control, Laws (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly, Liquor Control (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - General Assembly, Liquor Control, Pamphlets (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly, Road Fund (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly, Schools, 1933 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly, Message material, 1934 (Box 54, Folder 9-11)
  - General Assembly, Message (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - General Assembly, Message, 1934 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly, Message, Liquor Control, 1934 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - General Assembly, Message, Reports from Departments, 1934 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly, Message, Sales tax, 1934 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Gold (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Golden Rule Foundation (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Government, Veteran's Hospital (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Governmental expenditures (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Advisory Commission on Unemployment Insurance (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Conference, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
  - Governor's Conference, 1930-1931 (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
  - Governor's Conference, 1932 (Box 56, Folder 3-6)
  - Governor's Conference, Attendance, States, Alabama-Iowa (Box 56, Folder 7-22)
  - Governor's Conference, Attendance, States, Kansas-Wyoming (Box 57, Folder 1-35)
  - Governor's Conference, Entertainment (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Governor's Conference, Expenses (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - Governor's Conference, Flags (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Governor's Conference, Gifts (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - Governor's Conference, Memorandum, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Conference, Proceedings, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Conference, Speakers program, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Conference, Seating arrangement, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Conference, Staff, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Conference, Transportation, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Conference, 1933 (Box 58, Folder 7-10)
  - Governor's Mansion (Box 58, Folder 11-12)
  - Governor's Mansion (Box 59, Folder 1-3)
  - Governor's Office (Box 59, Folder 4-6)
  - Governor's Office, 1931 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Staff (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Gubernatorial campaign, Peery (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Gubernatorial platforms, 1933 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Gunston Hall Regents (Box 60, Folder 5-6)
  - Hall of Fame, New York University (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Hall of Fame, Virginia (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Hall of Fame (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
  - Hall of Fame, New busts (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Hall of Fame, George Rogers Clark (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Hall of Fame, Patrick Henry (Box 61, Folder 5-6)
  - Hall of Fame, Sam Houston (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Hall of Fame, Stonewall Jackson (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Hall of Fame, Joseph E. Johnston (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Hall of Fame, Fitzhugh Lee (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Hall of Fame, Richard Henry Lee (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Hall of Fame, Andrew Lewis (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Hall of Fame, Meriwether Lewis (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Hall of Fame, Cyrus H. McCormick (Box 61, Folder 14-15)
  - Hall of Fame, George Mason (Box 62, Folder 1-3)
  - Hall of Fame, Matthew Fontaine Maury (Box 62, Folder 4-5)
  - Hall of Fame, Sculptors (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Hall of Nations (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Health Commission (Box 62, Folder 8-9)
  - Health Commission, Board (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Health Commission, Bureau of Vital Statistics (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Health Commission, Crane, Richard (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Health Commission, Flannagan, Roy (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Health Commission, Sleeping Sickness Test (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Henry, Patrick (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Highway Commission (Box 63, Folder 7-8)
  - Highway Commission (Box 64, Folder 1-3)
  - Highway Commission (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
  - Highway Commission, Appointments (Box 65, Folder 3-4)
  - Highway Commission, Appointments (Box 66, Folder 1-6)
  - Highway Commission, Bridges (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Highway Commission, Byrd Road Plan (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Highway Commission, Counties (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Highway Commission, Drought (Box 67, Folder 4-5)
  - Highway Commission, Federal Aid (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Highway Commission, Landscape Engineer (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Highway Commission, Lee Highway (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Highway Commission, Planting (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Highway Commission, Tree Nursery (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Highway Commission, Washington Memorial Highway (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Highway Commission, Williamsburg By-Pass (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - History Conference (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Holidays (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Homebuilding and Home Ownership Conference (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Homecoming Year (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Homeless and Transients Conference (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Hospitals, Blue Ridge Sanatorium (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Hospitals, Catawba Sanatorium (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Hospitals, Central State (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Hospitals, Colony for Epileptics (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Hospitals, Diseased and Crippled Children (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Hospitals, Eastern State (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Hospitals, Mental cases (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Hospitals, Southwestern State (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Hospitals, Western State (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Hospitals, Western State, Thomas Yancey Investigation (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Inaugural Address (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Inauguration, Presidential (Box 69, Folder 6-12)
  - Indians (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Industrial Commission (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Industrial Commission, Reappointment letters (Box 70, Folder 1-2)
  - Industrial Commission, New Industries (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Commission, Survey (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Inquiries (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Institute of Public Affairs, 1933 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Insurance Commission (Box 70, Folder 7-8)
  - International Colonial Exposition (Paris, France) (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - International Typewriters Contest (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Invitations (Box 71, Folder 1-4)
  - Invitations (Box 72, Folder 1-4)
  - Invitations (Box 73, Folder 1-4)
  - Invitations (Box 74, Folder 1-6)
  - Invitations (Box 75, Folder 1-8)
  - Jennings Estate (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Judges (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Judges, Appointment, Recommendations for Civil Justices Court, Richmond City (Box 76, Folder 3-4)
  - Judges, Appointment, Recommendations for Corporation Court, Lynchburg (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Judges, Appointment, Recommendations for Hustins Court, Petersburg (Box 76, Folder 6-7)
  - Judges, Appointment, Judicial Circuits, 2nd (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Judges, Appointment, Judicial Circuits, 8th (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Judges, Appointment, Judicial Circuits, 12th (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Judges, Appointment, Judicial Circuits, 13th (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Judges, Appointment, Judicial Circuits, 16th (Box 76, Folder 12-14)
  - Judges, Appointment, Judicial Circuits, 16th (Box 77, Folder 1-3)
  - Judges, Appointment, Judicial Circuits, 27th (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Judges, Appointment, Judicial Circuits, 31st (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Judges, Appointment, Supreme Court of Appeals (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Judges, Designation of (Box 77, Folder 7-8)
  - Judges, Designation of (Box 78, Folder 1-3)
  - Judicial Council (Box 78, Folder 4-8)
  - Jury System (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Labor, Commissioner (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Labor, Commissioner (Box 79, Folder 1-4)
  - Labor Bureau of (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Lafayette Bust, Loan to Philadelphia (Box 79, Folder 6-7)
  - Land grants (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Law Enforcement (Box 79, Folder 9-10)
  - Law Enforcement (Box 80, Folder 1-5)
  - Law Enforcement (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Law Enforcement, Articles (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Law Enforcement, Bonus Army (Box 81, Folder 3-4)
  - Law Enforcement, Club Forest (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Law Enforcement, Colonial Beach (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Law Enforcement, Hunger Marchers (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Law Enforcement, Lindbergh baby (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Law Enforcement, Princess Anne County (Box 81, Folder 9-10)
  - Law Enforcement, Special Forces (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Law Enforcement, Strikes (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - League of Virginia Municipalities (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Lee Boulevard (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Lee, Robert E., Memorial Foundation (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Lee, Robert E., Statue Fund (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Reference Bureau (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Letters of Commendation (Box 82, Folder 5-6)
  - Letters of Commendation (Box 83, Folder 1-4)
  - Letters of Commendation (Box 84, Folder 1-5)
  - Letters of Commendation, Federal Patronage (Box 85, Folder 1-6)
  - Letters of Commendation, Federal Patronage (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Letters of Commendation, Harry F. Byrd (Box 86, Folder 2-3)
  - Lime Grinding Plants (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Lists, Appointments (Box 86, Folder 5-7)
  - Lynching (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - McCormick, Cyrus Hall (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Manufacturers Record (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Marine Museum (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Medical College of Virginia (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Membership (Box 87, Folder 3-4)
  - Merrimac-Monitor Park (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Military Board and Rifle Range (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Miller Manual School (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Milk reports (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Monroe Centennial Memorial Committee (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Monticello (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Mortgages (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
  - Mother's Day (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Motor vehicles, Director (Box 88, Folder 4-6)
  - Motor vehicles, Director (Box 89, Folder 1-4)
  - Motor Vehicles, Motor Safety (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Motor Vehicles, Motor Safety (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Motor Vehicles, Road Taxes (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Motor Vehicles, Special Police (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Mount Vernon, Board of Visitors (Box 90, Folder 4-5)
  - Mount Vernon, Ladies Association of the Union (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Multigraphed letters (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Narcotic Education (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - National Capital Park and Planning Commission (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - National Capital Port Authority (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - National Consumers League (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - National Economic League (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Club (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - National Flood Control (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - National Geographic Magazine (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - National Institute of Public Administration (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - National Museum of Ceramic Art (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Natural Bridge (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Nautical School (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Newspapers (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers, Subscriptions, 1929 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers, Subscriptions, 1930 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers, Subscriptions, 1931-1932 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers, Subscriptions, 1932-1933 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers, Subscriptions, 1933-1934 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Northern Virginia Park and Planning Committee (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Notaries Public, Appointments (Box 92, Folder 6-7)
  - Oakwood Cemetery (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Office Hours (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Old age pensions (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Payne, John Barton (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Peace (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Penitentiary (Box 93, Folder 3-5)
  - Penitentiary, Board (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Penitentiary, Commission to Study Sentences (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Penitentiary, Electrocutions (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Penitentiary, Insane Convicts (Box 94, Folder 2-3)
  - Penitentiary, Investigation, Camp #18 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Penitentiary, Jails (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Penitentiary, Road Force (Box 94, Folder 6-7)
  - Pensions for Public School Teachers and Others (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Petain, Marshall (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Requests for (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Politics (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Pollution, Commission (Box 94, Folder 12-13)
  - Portraits (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Positions, Requests for (Box 95, Folder 1-4)
  - Positions, Requests for (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Potomac River Bridge Commission (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Potomac River Commission (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - President of the United States (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - President's Camp on the Rapidan (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Prince of Wales (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Prisons and Crimes (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Proclamations, Office copies (Box 96, Folder 8-10)
  - Proclamations, Thanksgiving (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Prohibition (Box 97, Folder 2-4)
  - Prohibition (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Prohibition, 21st Amendment (Box 98, Folder 2-3)
  - Public printer (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Public Welfare, Commissioner (Box 98, Folder 5-7)
  - Public Welfare, Commissioner (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Public Welfare, Board (Box 99, Folder 2-3)
  - Publicity director (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Requests for (Box 99, Folder 5-7)
  - Purchasing and Printing, Director (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Purchasing and Printing, Confiscated cars (Box 100, Folder 1-4)
  - Purchasing and Printing, Confiscated cars (Box 101, Folder 1-3)
  - Purchasing and Printing, Confiscated cars, Investigation, Charges brought by Miss T.C. Edwards (Box 101, Folder 4-5)
  - Purchasing and Printing, Confiscated cars, Investigation, Charges brought by Miss T.C. Edwards (Box 102, Folder 1-3)
  - Purchasing and Printing, Confiscated cars, Investigation, Charges brought by Miss T.C. Edwards (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Queen Elizabeth, Portrait of (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Radio programs (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Rate Commission (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate Commission (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Reapportionment (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Red Cross (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Red Cross, Society of Yugoslavia (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Relief (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Religious liberty (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Reorganization of State Government (Box 103, Folder 11-12)
  - Repeal Convention, Luncheon (Box 104, Folder 1-2)
  - Reports, Printed (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Residents, New (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Restoration, Old Hall of House of Delegates (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Retirement Fund for state employees (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Rewards (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Rhodes Scholarship (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Richmond Academy of Arts (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Richmond Blues (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Richmond Community Funds (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac Railroad (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Rotary (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Safety Appliance Commission (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Seafood (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of State (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of War (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Serbian Dinner (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Shenandoah National Park (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Shenandoah National Park (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Short ballot (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Small loan (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Soldiers' Home (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Southern Cotton Festival (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Southern Woman's Educational Alliance (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Southwestern Virginia, Inc. (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Spanish-American War Veterans (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Standardization Board (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - State Art Museum (Box 106, Folder 10-11)
  - State Art Museum, Contributions (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - State Art Museum, John Barton Payne (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - State Art Museum, Soldiers' Home Property (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - State Boards, Canvassers (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - State Boards, Censors (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - State Boards, Public Welfare, Bureau of Mental Hygiene (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - State Boards, Public Welfare, Mother's Aid Fund (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - State Boards, Public Welfare, World War Service Division (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - State Comptroller (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - State Constabulary (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - State Depositories (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - State Employees (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - State Farm for Defective Misdemeanant (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - State Farm for Women (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - State Flower (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - State Geologist (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - State Horticultural Society (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - State Insurance on Property (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - State Library (Box 108, Folder 1-2)
  - State Library, Fire Proofing (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - State Library, Harrison Portrait Unveiling (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - State Lime Grinding Board (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - State Museum (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - State Port Authority (Box 108, Folder 7-8)
  - State Port Authority, Virginia Forwarding Corporation (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - State seal (Box 109, Folder 1-2)
  - State Teacher's College (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - State Teacher's College, East Radford (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - State Teacher's College, Farmville (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - State Teacher's College, Fredericksburg (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - State Teacher's College, Harrisonburg (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - State Treasurer (Box 109, Folder 8-9)
  - State Veterinary Association (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Statements, Missent (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Stone Mountain Confederate Memorial (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Storm relief, 1933 August (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Student loans (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Taxation (Box 110, Folder 1-3)
  - Taxation, Commissioner (Box 111, Folder 1-2)
  - Taxation, Bank (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Taxation, Commission of Division of Taxable Subjects (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Taxation, Delinquency (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Taxation, Reduction, 1930 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Taxation, Sales Tax (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Taylor, Zachary, 150th Anniversary (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Thrift (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Tobacco (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Truck Experiment Station (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Tuberculosis Association (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Unemployment, State Commission (Box 112, Folder 1-3)
  - Unemployment, Federal Appropriation (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Unemployment, Federal Commission (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Uniform State Laws (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - University of Virginia, 1934-1936 (Box 112, Folder 7-8)
  - University of Virginia, Board of Visitors (Box 113, Folder 1-4)
  - University of Virginia, Hospital (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - University of Virginia, Newsletter (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - United States, Dept. of Commerce, Bureau of Census (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - United States, Naval Academy (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - United States, Veterans Bureau, Review Board (Box 114, Folder 2-3)
  - United States, Veterans Hospital (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - United States, Veterans, Spanish War (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Valentine Memorial Association (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Valley Forge (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Vault (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Bar Association (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Born Presidents (Box 114, Folder 10-11)
  - Virginia Bureau of Research (Box 114, Folder 12-13)
  - Virginia Commission for the Blind (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Contractors (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Virginia-District of Columbia Boundary Line (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Finances (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Government (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Homecoming (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Industrial School Board for Colored Children (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Industrial School Board for White Children (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Industrial School Board for Colored Girls (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Journal of Education (Box 115, Folder 9-10)
  - Virginia League of Municipalities (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Manual Labor School (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Military Institute (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Military Institute (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Municipal Review (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Board of Visitors, Recommendations, J.S. Agnew (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Board of Visitors, Recommendations, T. Gilbert Wood (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Soil survey (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Real Estate Commission (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Virginia School for Colored Deaf and Blind Children (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Virginia School for Deaf and Blind (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Social Science Association (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Virginia State College for Negroes (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Virginia State Fair (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Union University (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - War Memorial Commission (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Washington, George, Bicentennial Birth Commission (Box 118, Folder 2-5)
  - Washington, George, Bicentennial Birth Commission (Box 119, Folder 1-4)
  - Washington, George, Cherry Farm (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Washington, George, Foundation for Citizenship and Education (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Washington, George, Fredericksburg Celebration (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Washington, George, Houdoun's Statue (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Washington, George, Memorial Athenaeum (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Washington, George, Memorial Parkway (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Washington, George, National Forest (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Washington, George, Wakefield (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Washington and Lee University (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - West Point Military Academy (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - White House Conference (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - William and Mary Conference (Box 120, Folder 8-9)
  - Williamsburg Holding Corp., Celebration (Box 120, Folder 10-11)
  - Williamsburg Holding Corp., Restoration (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Women's Compensation (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - World Court (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - World War, Military Order of (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - W.R.V.A. (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Y.M.C.A. (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Yorktown Sesqui-Centennial Commission (Box 121, Folder 6-9)
  - Yorktown Sesqui-Centennial Commission, State Representatives (Box 122, Folder 1-5)
  - Yorktown Sesqui-Centennial Commission, State Representatives (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Yorktown Sesqui-Centennial Commission, Thirteen Original States' Speeches (Box 123, Folder 2)
- Series II: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1930-1934., Extent: 2.45 cu. ft. (7 boxes). (Box Boxes 123-129)
  The Miscellaneous Correspondence series, 1930-1934 is housed in seven archival boxes and is arranged alphabetically by subject. This series documents correspondence received and sent by Governor Pollard during his four-year term as governor of Virginia. In addition to correspondence, there are reports, proclamations, telegrams, orders, resolutions, acts, publications, news clippings, invitations, proceedings, financial statements, invoices, and other sundry items.
  - A (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Alabama, Governor of (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Arizona, Governor of (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Arkansas, Governor of (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - B (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Bands (Box 124, Folder 1)